[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the national flower of Mexico and Columbia, introduced to Europe as late as the end of the 19th century?", "correct_answer": "Dahlia", "incorrect_answers": ["Lilac", "Iris", "Rose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Bernie and Roz Fockers little dog in the 2004 comedy movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "Moses", "incorrect_answers": ["Abraham", "Isaak", "Jeremiah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marlon Wayans was in the movie Above the Rim with Tupac.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Angelina Jolie co-stars with this actor in the 2001 movie Original Sin.", "correct_answer": "Antonio Banderas", "incorrect_answers": ["Denzel Washington", "George Clooney", "Johnny Depp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many fatal brown and grizzly bear attacks have been reported between 1900 and 2003 in North America?", "correct_answer": "53", "incorrect_answers": ["175", "542", "257"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tiny island of M\u00e4rket / M\u00e4rketin in the Baltic Sea is shared by these two nations.", "correct_answer": "Finland and Sweden", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden and Denmark", "Finland and Estonia", "Finland and Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of ginger is contraindicated in cases of this medical condition.", "correct_answer": "Gallstones", "incorrect_answers": ["Diarrhea", "Pregnancy", "Kidney stones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This drink is a widely known stimulant, but if you have too much, it becomes a depressant. Its active ingredient - caffeine - is known as the worlds most popular drug.", "correct_answer": "Coffee", "incorrect_answers": ["Water", "Orange juice", "Tea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On December 7, 1941 the Japanese launched a sneak attack on Pearl Harbor. On that day they also launched a similar attack on this American airbase in the Philippines.", "correct_answer": "Angeles, Pampanga, Philippines", "incorrect_answers": ["Subic Bay, Luzon, Philippines", "Capas Air Base,Tarlac, Philippines", "Clark Air Force Base, Pampanga, Philippines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Dakota Fannings character in the 2004 movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "Lupita", "incorrect_answers": ["Patricia", "Palomita", "Paulina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Shortly after WWII, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention was founded in this city that hosted the 1939 premiere of Gone With the Wind.", "correct_answer": "Atlanta, GA", "incorrect_answers": ["Nashville, TN", "Birmingham, AL", "Raleigh, NC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This psychiatrist, founder of Analytical Psychology, made the following observation:  The more critical reasoning dominates, the more impoverished life becomes.", "correct_answer": "Carl Jung", "incorrect_answers": ["Juri Allik", "Sigmund Freud", "Alfred Adler"]}]